<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Venkatachalam</title><link>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Venkatachalam</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 22:26:09 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://venkyyuvy.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cons of too much delayed Gratificaiton</title><link>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/blogs/delayed_gratification/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 22:26:09 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/blogs/delayed_gratification/</guid><description>Why too much of delayed gratification is an issue? Someone can become good at delayed gratification but too much of delay / deffering it is a big problem. He / she may not be able to enjoy at the moment of gratification even when gratification happens after the desire amount of delay. The only thing that gives them happiness is delaying the gratification longer and longer - for anything at any point of anytime.</description></item><item><title>Ireland culture</title><link>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/blogs/corporate_experience/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 21:28:43 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/blogs/corporate_experience/</guid><description>When one person says, that he is going to get married. The reaction from others I hope this is your first time. Take good number of days leave man, we don&amp;rsquo;t get to do these things often.
After a person come back to office after the wedding, questions asked by the team members were,
Am I right in saying that you were married now? when asked priest that important question, does everybody said okay?</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/about/start/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 12:05:33 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/about/start/</guid><description>Hi!!!
Thanks for visiting my website. My name is Venkatachalam Natchiappan. I am currently working as a senior data scientist in Ericsson. All time fan of Yuvraj Singh (Ex-Indian cricket team player). My strengths are Machine learning, operations research and software engineering. Prior to the current role, I was working as a Data scientist in Machine learning, centre of excellence team of Ford&amp;rsquo;s Global Data Insights and analytics team. I have working on developing vehicle routing solutions using genetic algorithm, constraint programming in the OR space.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/blogs/savings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/blogs/savings/</guid><description>After a sudden plan of removing my wisdom tooth, which I had been delaying for more than 6 years. On that day, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t able to drive the car to Chennai. I requested my friends to suggest any acting-drivers for driving our car from Mayiladuthurai to Chennai. Initially, one friend called me back and said he found someone, who would charge 2K for it. I took a back seat because I didn&amp;rsquo;t expect this much charge for 250 Kms drive rather I was expecting around 1000 to 1500.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/fitness/left_knee/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/fitness/left_knee/</guid><description>Oct 2012:
I had my first injury to left knee during the zonal semi-finals match with REC (Rajalakshmi college of engineering), happened in our college (College of Engineering, Guindy). One opponent&amp;rsquo;s knee hit my left knee on the medial side. Immediatley I felt a shock on my nerve and after that I couldn&amp;rsquo;t continue my play on that match. On the same day, during the warmup for the final match - my left knee collapsed when I try to make a feint to Tamilvanan (who is standing as a defender for me) and took off for a shoot.</description></item></channel></rss>