<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Venkatachalam Natchiappan</title><link>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Venkatachalam Natchiappan</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 12:05:33 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://venkyyuvy.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/about/start/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 12:05:33 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/about/start/</guid><description/></item><item><title>comnset</title><link>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/photos/comsnet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/photos/comsnet/</guid><description>COMNSET conference 2023 in Bangalore, India.</description></item><item><title>handball</title><link>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/photos/handball/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/photos/handball/</guid><description>In Anna Univeristy CEG Handball court during the Tamilvanan memorial trophy.</description></item><item><title>profile_picture</title><link>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/photos/profile_picture/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/photos/profile_picture/</guid><description/></item><item><title>sikkim</title><link>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/photos/sikkim/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/photos/sikkim/</guid><description>During our tour to Sikkim in Oct 2022</description></item><item><title>Cons of too much delayed gratificaiton</title><link>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/blogs/delayed_gratification/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 22:26:09 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/blogs/delayed_gratification/</guid><description>Why too much of delayed gratification is an issue? Someone can become good at delayed gratification but too much of delay / deffering it is a big problem. He / she may not be able to enjoy at the moment of gratification even when gratification happens after the desire amount of delay. The only thing that gives them happiness is delaying the gratification longer and longer - for anything at any point of anytime.</description></item><item><title>left_knee</title><link>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/lifestyle/left_knee/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 22:26:09 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/lifestyle/left_knee/</guid><description>Oct 2012:
I had my first injury to left knee during the zonal semi-finals match with REC (Rajalakshmi college of engineering), happened in our college (College of Engineering, Guindy). One opponent&amp;rsquo;s knee hit my left knee on the medial side. Immediatley I felt a shock on my nerve and after that I couldn&amp;rsquo;t continue my play on that match. On the same day, during the warmup for the final match - my left knee collapsed when I try to make a feint to Tamilvanan (who is standing as a defender for me) and took off for a shoot.</description></item><item><title>parenting</title><link>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/lifestyle/parenting/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 22:26:09 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/lifestyle/parenting/</guid><description>Give all the opinions as suggestions; we shouldn&amp;rsquo;t take the decision from their place.
All they need from the parents is TIME!!!
Letting them ask questions without any reservations on whom to ask and what to ask initially. Gradually, help them understand what is appropriate. Thinking loud and making them feel that it is okay to not understand things and be open about it. There is nothing inferior about not know anything in this world.</description></item><item><title>Savings</title><link>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/blogs/savings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 22:26:09 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/blogs/savings/</guid><description>After a sudden plan of removing my wisdom tooth, which I had been delaying for more than 6 years. On that day, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t able to drive the car to Chennai. I requested my friends to suggest any acting-drivers for driving our car from Mayiladuthurai to Chennai. Initially, one friend called me back and said he found someone, who would charge 2K for it. I took a back seat because I didn&amp;rsquo;t expect this much charge for 250 Kms drive rather I was expecting around 1000 to 1500.</description></item><item><title>Ireland culture</title><link>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/blogs/corporate_experience/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 21:28:43 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/blogs/corporate_experience/</guid><description>One person in an online meeting says that he is going to get married. The reaction from rest of the members in the team: - I hope this is your first time! - Take good number of days off man, one don&amp;rsquo;t get to do these things often!!
When the person come back to office after the wedding, questions asked by the team members were,
- Am I right in saying that you were married now?</description></item><item><title>Ergonomics</title><link>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/lifestyle/ergonomics/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 21:28:43 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/lifestyle/ergonomics/</guid><description>NO poster is ideal so that it can be maintained for long hours or consistently for many days. Constantly changing the poster is a good trick to make sure, we are not straining a certain parts of our body.
Few rule of thumbs that I gathered over the years:
Keep the two - third (2/3) of the screen/monitor above the eye-level. (Learned this very useful tip from Flavio) Make sure your foot is grounded on some surface so that the leg maintains 90 degrees with the floor.</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/projects/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 21:28:43 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/projects/</guid><description>1. QnA for Policy control Large language model based QnA model for PCF system.
2. Remote interference management Graph based ML solution to observe and detect remote interference in 5G networks.
3. Network Milestone completion time estimation Model trees to predict the time to complete different milestones of network rollout project. Publication in COMSNETS 2023; Best paper award in MINDS workshop
4. Traffic classification in Packet core Identify the mobile application and classifying the type of user actions (send/receive message, file transfer, voice or video calls) based on first few encrypted packets of TCP or UDP flow.</description></item><item><title>Trekking</title><link>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/photos/trekking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/photos/trekking/</guid><description>Trekking in Kudremukh, during Dec 2017.</description></item></channel></rss>