<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lifestyles on Venkatachalam Natchiappan</title><link>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/lifestyle/</link><description>Recent content in Lifestyles on Venkatachalam Natchiappan</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 22:26:09 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://venkyyuvy.github.io/lifestyle/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>left_knee</title><link>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/lifestyle/left_knee/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 22:26:09 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/lifestyle/left_knee/</guid><description>Oct 2012:
I had my first injury to left knee during the zonal semi-finals match with REC (Rajalakshmi college of engineering), happened in our college (College of Engineering, Guindy). One opponent&amp;rsquo;s knee hit my left knee on the medial side. Immediatley I felt a shock on my nerve and after that I couldn&amp;rsquo;t continue my play on that match. On the same day, during the warmup for the final match - my left knee collapsed when I try to make a feint to Tamilvanan (who is standing as a defender for me) and took off for a shoot.</description></item><item><title>parenting</title><link>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/lifestyle/parenting/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 22:26:09 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/lifestyle/parenting/</guid><description>Give all the opinions as suggestions; we shouldn&amp;rsquo;t take the decision from their place.
All they need from the parents is TIME!!!
Letting them ask questions without any reservations on whom to ask and what to ask initially. Gradually, help them understand what is appropriate. Thinking loud and making them feel that it is okay to not understand things and be open about it. There is nothing inferior about not know anything in this world.</description></item><item><title>Ergonomics</title><link>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/lifestyle/ergonomics/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 21:28:43 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/lifestyle/ergonomics/</guid><description>NO poster is ideal so that it can be maintained for long hours or consistently for many days. Constantly changing the poster is a good trick to make sure, we are not straining a certain parts of our body.
Few rule of thumbs that I gathered over the years:
Keep the two - third (2/3) of the screen/monitor above the eye-level. (Learned this very useful tip from Flavio) Make sure your foot is grounded on some surface so that the leg maintains 90 degrees with the floor.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/lifestyle/appreciation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/lifestyle/appreciation/</guid><description>Appreciation What is appreciation?
Anything that makes you feel better than the so called NORMAL.
when I walked into one of my school friends home, her father told me with a big smiling face that he liked the way I parked the car!!! There is nothing special or extraordinary about it. but still he wanted share his happiness with me. He goes on to say that I parked the car with ease ( meaning not making many adjustments to arive at the final position).</description></item><item><title/><link>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/lifestyle/investments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/lifestyle/investments/</guid><description>Popular class of investments Equity stocks ETFs Mutual Funds Debts Fixed deposits Recurring deposits (chits) Corporate bonds Gold Physical gold Soverign Bonds ETFs Bitcoins PF/ PPF Real Estates Things which are not investments Home Car Insurance policies Jewels Keeping it as cash Inflation Inflation rate is the rate at which the general goods and service cost changes in an economy.
The chart below shows the change in inflation rate for India over the years.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/lifestyle/rest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/lifestyle/rest/</guid><description>Dr. Saundra Dalton-Smith
Seven types of rest
Physical rest Passive: 7+ hours or power naps Active: stretch, massage or ergonomic seating
Mental rest Overtaxing your thinking
Write down your todos Reference checklists (packing, groceries, etc.) Shutdown ritual to separate work and life Take a break from problem-solving Meditate Social rest Evaluate your relationships
Spend more time with people who give you energy Spend less time with people who steal your energy If you&amp;rsquo;re an introvert, block out time to be alone Spiritual rest Be part of something bigger than yourself.</description></item></channel></rss>