<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blogs on Venkatachalam Natchiappan</title><link>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/blogs/</link><description>Recent content in Blogs on Venkatachalam Natchiappan</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 22:26:09 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://venkyyuvy.github.io/blogs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cons of too much delayed gratificaiton</title><link>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/blogs/delayed_gratification/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 22:26:09 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/blogs/delayed_gratification/</guid><description>Why too much of delayed gratification is an issue? Someone can become good at delayed gratification but too much of delay / deffering it is a big problem. He / she may not be able to enjoy at the moment of gratification even when gratification happens after the desire amount of delay. The only thing that gives them happiness is delaying the gratification longer and longer - for anything at any point of anytime.</description></item><item><title>Savings</title><link>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/blogs/savings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 22:26:09 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/blogs/savings/</guid><description>After a sudden plan of removing my wisdom tooth, which I had been delaying for more than 6 years. On that day, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t able to drive the car to Chennai. I requested my friends to suggest any acting-drivers for driving our car from Mayiladuthurai to Chennai. Initially, one friend called me back and said he found someone, who would charge 2K for it. I took a back seat because I didn&amp;rsquo;t expect this much charge for 250 Kms drive rather I was expecting around 1000 to 1500.</description></item><item><title>Ireland culture</title><link>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/blogs/corporate_experience/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 21:28:43 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://venkyyuvy.github.io/blogs/corporate_experience/</guid><description>One person in an online meeting says that he is going to get married. The reaction from rest of the members in the team: - I hope this is your first time! - Take good number of days off man, one don&amp;rsquo;t get to do these things often!!
When the person come back to office after the wedding, questions asked by the team members were,
- Am I right in saying that you were married now?</description></item></channel></rss>